

າ Van Chi Axel

Route du Bois 49b. Ecublens. Switzerland

📕 +41 78 960 16 50 | 💌 axeldvc@gmail.com | extstyle extstyle

in linkedin.com/in/axel-dinh-van-chi/

Personal Profile

Freshly graduated of EPFL's Computational Science and Engineering Master program, I am a highly skilled and motivated individual with a strong background in mathematics, computer science, and engineering. Through my coursework and research projects, I have developed expertise in a wide range of areas, including deep learning, computer vision and numerical simulations.

Education

École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne, EPFL

Lausanne, Switzerland

Sen 2020 - Mar 2023

M.Sc. in Computational Science and Engineering

- Student Assistant for the Machine Learning Course in automn 2021.
- · Private Teacher in Mathematics and Physics.
- Courses: Deep Learning, Machine Learning, Applied Data Analysis, Image Processing 1, Advanced Numerical Analysis, Numerical Integration of Dynamical Systems, Parallel and High-Performance Computing, Software Engineering

École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne, EPFL

Lausanne, Switzerland

B.Sc. in Mathematics

Sep 2015 - Sep 2020

Work Experience

Cusco 11, Restaurant Lausanne, Switzerland

Restaurant Manager

Mar 2023 - Apr 2023

• Team management, waiter during both lunch and dinner shifts.

Sony Europe B.V.

Stuttgart, Germany

Research Intern in Computational Imaging

Apr 2022 - Sep 2022

- Interpolation of densely measured BRDF data for rendering. Doing so, the reflectance properties of isotropic material could be acquired in around 5 minutes against 8 hours prior the project.
- Implementation using Python and C++. For rendering, the Mitsuba 2 and Unreal Engine softwares were used.
- Technical Skills: Python with PyTorch, NumPy, Matplotlib, Pandas, Scikit-learn, C++, OpenGL, Slurm, Ubuntu Linux, Linux tools, Apt, Scripting,
- Soft Skills: Communication, Presentation skills.

Projects

Personal Project

Reinforcement Learning Library Implementation

• Development of a reinforcement learning library for learning purpose.

Apr 2023 - Aug 2023

- Technical Skills: Reinforcement Learning, Documentation, Python Packaging
- **Master Project: Motion Correction in Cardiac MRIs**

École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne, Computer Vision Laboratory

Lausanne, Switzerland

Oct 2022 - Mar 2023

- Deep Learning based extraction of Left Ventricles in MRIs. · Using pure post-processing methods we improved the overall quality of the MRI scans, avoiding redundant uses of MRI scanner, which are both time-consuming and expensive.
- **Technical Skills:** PyTorch, PyTorch Lightning, WandB, Slurm.
- Soft Skills: Presentation skills, Report writing.

PDE Solving using Deep Learning

Lausanne, Switzerland

École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne, Chair of Computational Mathematics and Simulation Science

Sep 2021 - Feb 2022

- Implementation of a Variational Physics-Informed Neural Network framework capable of handling imaginary numbers.
- · Experiments made on the Helmholtz equation.

Transfer-Learning in Natural Language Processing

Lausanne, Switzerland

École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne, Machine Learning and Optimization Laboratory

Mar 2021 - Jun 2021

• Study of the finetuning of Bert model by freezing 99.9% of its weights. • Technical Skills: Natural Language Processing, Hugging Face.

Mobile Application Development

Personal Project

- Integration of a finetuned PyTorch NLP model used as a ChatBot which must reply using a predefined answers database.
- Technical Skills: Android Studio, Flutter.

Skills

Programming Python (Pandas, PyTorch, NumPy, Scikit-learn, Seaborn, etc...), CUDA, OpenMPI, Matlab, C++, ŁTEX, Slurm, Git, Markdown.

Engineering Simulation of ODEs and PDEs, Linear Algebra and Matrix Theory, Computer Vision, Signal Processing, Statistics.

Soft Skills Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation, Engaging Presentation.

Languages.

English Professional proficiency French Native proficiency

Interests.

I enjoy cooking on my free-time, especially Italian cuisine.

Sports

Coming from a city along the sea, I love to wake board and surf. During my time in Switzerland, I could easily access the mountains

to snowboard.